Finding Aid for the Dewey Daane Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 13 Greene, 4/10/85 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 14 J.D.D., 4/17/85 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- Student Paper Topics, 1985 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- Spring, 1984 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 1 J.D.D., 1/11/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- Memos to the President, 1/11/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 2 Cox, 1/18/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 3 Yeo, 1/25/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 4 Holland, 2/1/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 5 Corrigan, 2/8/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 6 Penner, 2/11/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 7 Sternlight, 2/22/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 8 Keehn, 2/29/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 9 Leonard, 3/14/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 10 Solomon, 3/21/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 11 Deming, 3/28/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 12 Greene, 4/4/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 13 Morris, 4/11/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 14 J.D.D., 4/18/84 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- Paper Topics, 1984 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- Spring, 1983 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 1 J.D.D., 1/12/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 1 J.D.D., 1/12/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- Memos to the President, 1/12/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 2 Donald L. Koch, 1/19/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 3 Edwin H. Yeo III, 1/26/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 4 E. Gerald Corrigan, 2/2/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 5 Irwin D. Sandberg, 2/9/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 6 Rudolph G. Penner, 2/16/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 7 Eugene A. Leonard, 2/23/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 8 Silas Keehn, 3/2/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 9 Frederick L. Deming, 3/16/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 10 Frank E. Morris, 3/23/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 11 Karen N. Horn, 3/30/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 12 Margaret L. Greene, 4/6/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 13 Roger E. Brinner, 4/13/83 (Box 92)
- Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy- 14 J.D.D., 4/20/83 (Box 92)
- Money and Banking- 1, 2/17/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 2, 2/19/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 3, 2/24/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 4, 2/26/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 5, 3/10/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 6, 3/12/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 7, 3/17/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 8, 3/19/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 9, 3/24/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 10, 3/26/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 11, 3/31/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 12, 4/2/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 13 and 14, 4/7/75 and 4/9/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 15, 4/14/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 16, 4/16/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 17, 4/21/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 18, 4/23/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- Quiz (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- 19, 4/28/75 (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- Final Exam, 4/30/75 (Box 93)
- Wallich Reading Lists for Money and Banking Vanderbilt Reading Lists for Money and Banking Money and Banking Outlines (Box 93)
- Money and Banking- Final Exams (Box 93)
- Money and Banking (AIB) (Box 93)
- Lateral File #1 Drawer #1
  - International Financial Conference (April 8-11, 1984 Vienna, Austria)
  - International Financial Conference (May 29- June 4, 1983, Burgenstock, Switzerland) Itineraries-, 1977-1978
  - International Financial Conference
  - International Advisory Group
  - International Banking Act, 1978
  - Background Memos on International Contacts
  - International Dept- Correspondence
  - Testimony before General Assembly Re. Industrial Revue Bonds) Nov 30, 1981 President Carter’s Statement on Inflation, 4/15/77
  - Interest Rate Ceiling, Brook Bill
  - Institute on International Finance Directory, 1986
  - International Memoranda
  - Interoffice Memos (Misc.)
  - Blue Cross- Blue Shield 1981 Claims
  - Medical Insurance, 1981-1982
  - Medical Insurance, 1983
  - Medical Insurance, 1984
  - SE US/ Japanese Joint Meeting, Hot Springs, VA, 10/12-14/86
  - Tokyo, Japan 10/12-14/85 Japan/ US SE
  - Japan Association
  - Victoria Jackson
  - Bank of Japan
  - Remarks to Businessmen’s Luncheon, Johnson City, TN, 7/21/76
  - Temporary Organizing Committee, JFK School of Gov. Assn. Meeting 5/18/77 Kennedy Library Status Report
  - Fed Papers to JFK Library
  - Kekst and Co. of NY
  - Knoxville Seminar
  - Aubrey G. Langston and Co.
  - Leadership Nashville
  - Latin America Trip 1/77 JDD and Alfalfa Club
  - Lewis Levine
  - Library Committee- General
  - Loan Policy Committee Information
  - London- Speech, Symposium for Central Bankers, 11/11/75
  - London, NY, Zurich Trip, 9/10-20/75
  - London, A Symposium for Central Bankers, 11/11/75
  - London Office
  - LA- Dinner for Mr. Earthman 6/21/77
  - LA- Chamber of Commerce, Annual Meeting, Speech, 10/26/77
  - Manley Fellowship, JFK School of Government
  - Elizabeth MacDonald Manning Finance Magazine
  - William McChesney Martin
  - Memphis Trip, 3/10-11/75- Vanderbilt
  - Memphis Trip, 3/21/75- MSU
  - Memphis Trip Seminar on International Economics, 11/6/75
  - Memphis Trip Corporate Luncheon Speech, 3/21/77
  - Memphis Trip Speech Economic Colloquium, 4/18/77
  - Memphis Trip with Dean Richmond and Steve Waterman to Address Local Businessmen, 3/22-23/78
  - Mexico- 11/4/86- 2:30 pm
  - Mexico Meeting 11/17/86, Mr. Rainey’s Office 3:30 Mexico City- Calling Trip, 3/13-17/86
  - Michigan Vacation- August 1988 Michigan Vacation, 1988
  - Misc. Michigan Vacation File for, 1987
  - Montego Bay, Jamaica, May 1984
  - Montego Bay, Jamaica- Coroon and Black, 5/23-24/84
  - Information for Nashville Mortgage Bankers Association 12/15/76 Speech- Not Given Mobile, AL- Southern Association of Chamber of Commerce, Presidents Meeting 3/15/77 Speech
  - George S. Moore
  - Negotiations re: Mortgage Act
  - Mobile Speech, 3/15/77
  - Frank Morris Arthritis Award 12/2/88- Dinner Boston MA
  - National Association of Business Economists
  - National Futures Association
  - NABE Legislative Review Committee
  - Nashville Symphony
  - Banking Industry Speech and Bank Stock Symposium, Financial Analysts Federation, 4/9-10/75 NY
  - NYSE Index
  - Newspaper Articles re: Patwan Criticisms, July 1975
  - Newspaper Clippings
  - Newspaper Articles, 1975
  - Nissan Company
  - North Carolina National Bank (NCNB)
  - John Odell
  - OPEC
  - Operating Committee
  - Overseas Bankers Club
  - Patterson School- General File
  - Patterson School- Expense Information
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors, 4/9-11/87
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors Lexington, KY, 4/11-13/85
  - University of Kentucky- Lexington, KY Board of Advisors Patterson School 10/12-14/84 Patterson School- Board of Advisors, 10/13-16/83
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors, 4/15/83
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors, October 1981
  - Cary Blankenship, Patterson Student
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors, 9/18-21/80
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors-, 10/11-14/79
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors-, 4/19-21/79
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors- April 1979 Did Not Attend
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors-, 4/13-16/78
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors-, 10/13-16/77
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors, 4/14-17/77
  - Patterson School- Visit, Nov 12, 1976
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors-, 10/14-17/76
  - Patterson School- Board of Advisors-, 4/8-10/76
  - Patterson School of Diplomacy Board of Advisors, 4/10-11/75
  - PEFCO (Robert B. Rivel)
  - Personal
  - Photos of JDD
  - Photos of JDD
  - Personnel Placement Service
  - Piping Rook Club, Locust Valley, NY, 5/24/83
  - Loss- Ramada Imperial Inn- Lexington, KY, 4/10/75
  - President William Seidman and William Gorog
  - Press Releases
- Lateral File #1 Drawer #2
  - May 29-Jun 1, 1983 International Finance Committee- Burgenstock Switzerland 1985 for East Trip
  - Envelope-European Trip Jun 10-28, 1984 with Dennis Bottorff and D. Anderson Envelope- Misc.
  - Envelope- June 2-10, 19830 Switzerland?
  - European Trip- 1984 In and Out Correspondence
  - European Trip-, 1983
  - Receipts and Misc. Apr 8-13, 1984
  - European Trip Information, June 1982
  - European Trip 1984 (Bettie’s File)
  - European Trip Work File, June 1984
  - European Trip-, June 1981
  - European Trip-, June 1980
  - European Trip Information, 1979
  - European Trip-, June 1978
  - European Trip June 7-27, 1979
  - European Trip (General), June 1975
  - European Trip (London), June 1975
  - Expense Trip- European Trip, May 28-Jun 12, 1975
  - Banque de France- Exercise 1974- Compte Rendu
  - Swiss Credit Bank 118th Annual Report, 1974
  - European Trip (Basle- BIS Meeting), Jun 1975
  - European Trip(Frankfurt)-, Jun 1975
  - European Trip (Paris)-, Jun 1975
  - Bank Dossiers Paris, London and Frankfurt
  - Earthman’s Thank You Letters European Trip, Jun 1976
  - Proceedings at Annual BIS Meeting
  - BIS Annual Report and Related Material
  - Annual Meeting BIS Basle, Jun 12-14, 1976
  - Remarks to Officers re: Manila
  - Invitations, IMF Meetings Manila, 1976
  - TVB Cocktail Reception, IMF Meetings Manila, Oct 6, 1976
  - DC- Volcker Dinner Meeting, 1/2/85
  - Todd Christian Bottorff Resume
  - Resumes
  - NY Reception for JDD
  - Restaurant
  - Gregory Mallek Resume
  - Resumes
  - Retreat, Fall Creek Falls, 1975
  - Reunion- Duke University
  - Pierre Rinfret
  - Jamie Louis Robertson
  - Rome
  - Rome- Meeting, Jan 1974
  - Robert V. Roosa- Brown Brothers Harriman and Co.
  - Russia (and Hungary)
  - Reunion, High School Class- Traverse City, MI- Vacation and Reunion, June/July 1985
  - Richmond, Savings Bond Controversy
  - MA Schapiro and Co., INC
  - Dorothy Sellers- Judgeship
  - Solomon Brothers Comments
  - Speeches 1978 L. William Seidman, visit to Nashville Mar 29-30, 1976 1988 Sports Spectacular/SFC Tennis JDD and DCB
  - Stamford, Conn Conference, Dec 7, 1982
  - State Delegations 11/80 Election Results
  - Thomas Storrs- Belk Dinner, May 7, 1980
  - Gengo Syzuki, Association of Japanese Bank LTD.
  - Swan Ball, 1983
  - Taiwan, 1979
  - Meeting with Taylor, 6/10/85
  - Telegrams
  - FEI’s Southern Area Conference, Apr 21-23, 1977
  - Tennessee Bankers Association Meeting Memphis, May 12-13, 1975
  - Tennessee Bankers Association, Bob Gilliam, President
  - Tennessee Forestry Association Speech, May 8, 1980
  - Joseph H. Torrence
  - The Secretary of Treasury- Letters
  - NY Treasurer’s Luncheon-, Dec 4, 1987
  - NY Treasurer’s Luncheon-, Dec 5, 1986
  - NY Treasurer’s Luncheon-, Dec 6, 1985
  - NY Treasurer’s Luncheon-, Dec 10, 1984
  - Merlyn N. Trued
  - Huntington M. Turner
  - Tax Reform Act
  - Usury Ceiling Legislation, 1979
  - Oscar M. Uhler, Swiss Credit Bank
  - United Nations, Panel of Specialists for Establishment of Investment Bank for ACP Group of Countries
  - Union Miniere
  - Vanderbilt Commencement Schedules
  - Vanderbilt Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy Spring 1986 Vanderbilt Class Schedule Spring, 1985
  - Vanderbilt Class Schedule, Jan 11- Apr 18, 1984
  - Vanderbilt Class Schedules
  - Vanderbilt Class Evaluations, 1980
  - Vanderbilt- Misc. Correspondence
  - Vanderbilt Law Review
  - Alexander Heard- VU
  - Owen- Misc.
- Lateral File #1 Draw #3
  - Council of Economic Advisors Seminar 9/7/77- VU Council on Government Relations (VU Committee) Banks and People- Kevin McDonald
  - VU Alumnus Magazine- Spring 1977 Vol. 62 No 3 Personnel File for VU Students
  - Resumes- VU Students
  - VU- Betty Elder
  - Information- Alumni Groups- VU
  - VU- Faculty Senate
  - VU- Search Committee
  - Firozeh Bahmanyar
  - Holly Caldwell
  - Steven McDowell Campbell
  - Bernard Digeon- Student- VU
  - Valley Fidelity
  - Valley Fidelity
  - Vacation- Elk Rapids, MI, July 30-Sep 3, 1978
  - Volker (Meetings and Dinners), May 7, 1985
  - Volker (Meetings and Dinners), Jun 7, 1984
  - Volker (Meetings and Dinners), Sep 3, 1985
  - Volker (Meetings and Dinners), Sep 11, 1984
  - Volker (Meetings and Dinners), Dec 1982
  - Volkswagen
  - Dr. Henry C. Wallich, Board of Governors
  - Washington Trip, 1/9/78 JDD, Bottorff and Keller
  - Policies for Economic Recovery, Speech, Conference of American Society for Public Administration, DC 10/8/75
  - American Society for Public Administration, Conference, DC 10/8/75
  - Washington D.C. Trip- President Ford, 1/8/75
  - Washington D.C. Trip- Bernstein Party, Dec 17, 1974
  - Washington D.C. Trip- Dedication of Tennis Courts, 11/27/74
  - Washington D.C. Trip- Dedication of Building, 11/19/74
  - Watts Line- JDD
  - Murray L. Weidman Visit, 4/22-23/75
  - Bob Wilmoum Visit
  - Ralph and Kate Winter
  - Wine Information
  - Wychmere Harbor Conference 10/28-30/81 The Future of the Thrift Industry
  - Lee Youngdahl
  - Antoine W. Yameogo, IMF
  - Zaire, 1979
  - Financial Regulation Folder
  - TN Valley Bank Corps
  - Board of Governors Meeting 11/5/76 Hound Ears, NC
  - Denny Bottorff
  - CUB By-Laws
  - TVB Bylines
  - CUB Capital Planning
  - CUB Cash Management Forum 3/14-15/78 Opryland Hotel- Attended 14th Dinner only TVB Cash Management Forum 11/9/76- Speech
  - TVB- MSU Investment Seminar
  - Credit Policies and Procedures
  - Brownlee Curry
  - JDD- Vice Chairman- TVB
  - TVB- Letters of Congratulations on Appointment at CUB
  - William F. Earthman
  - Master List of Invitees to Daane Cocktail Party, Oct 15, 1974
  - Jimmy Gallivan
  - Pat Harrison
  - Jerre Hasview
  - Dan Hopkins- Chattanooga
  - CUB- International Dept.
  - International Department- Correspondence
  - International Department- Meeting with Directors, 10/20/76
  - International Monthly Business Development Meeting, 1/10/78
  - International Business Development Meeting, 4/31/78
  - TVB Reference and Misc.
  - TVB Pension Plan
  - TVB Officers and Directors Questionnaires
  - CUB Operating Committee Meeting 1/19/78- Discuss Job Posting
  - CUB Misc. Correspondence
  - Edward G. Nelson
  - CUB New Building
  - TVB Meeting Dates, Committees, Bylaws
  - Near Term International Game Plan
  - TVB 5year Corporate Plan 1977 Corporate Plan- International Department
  - US Human Rights Policies vis-à-vis CUB International Interests TVB Proxy Statements
  - NY Meeting re: TVB Perspective, 12/15/76
  - TVB Perspective- Autumn, 1976
  - TVB Perspective- Summer, 1976
  - TVB Perspective- (Bob Bennett) 1st Issue, May/June 1976
  - TVB Perspective- June 1978 JDD and George Moore
  - TVB Perspective- May/June Issue, 1977
  - TVB Perspective-, January 1977
  - CUB/TVB 1975 Profit Planning 1978 Profit Planning Meeting, Oct 12. 1977
  - William G. Simms
  - Robert H. Smith
  - CUB- Trust Department
  - Washington Representative Office- CUB
  - Pam West
  - Commerce Union Bank”1980 Reduction Program”
  - Bank Questionnaires
  - Chicago Board of Trade Meeting, 1/15/80
  - Harvard Alumni Directory, 1982
  - Asset Policy and Review Committee Meeting of, 8/22/88
  - National Futures Association
  - Patterson School Board of Advisors Lexington, KY 1986 Conference on Bank Structure and Competition 5/14-16/85- Chicago International Policy Committee Meeting, 10/26/87
  - International Policy Committee Meeting Oct 26, 1987- JDD International Policy Committee Meeting Oct 26, 1987- Bettie Adams International Policy Committee Meeting Oct 26, 1987 Bob Shell International Policy Committee Oct 26, 1987 3:00pm
  - Prochnow Graduate School of Banking- Madison Wisconsin University of Wisconsin- Graduate School of Banking- 1983 Session Wisconsin School of Banking Material, 1982
- Lateral File #1 Drawer #4
  - Kathryn Hall
  - Thomas Jay Hammond
  - Philip J. Olsson- VU
  - Ann Rosenstein- VU Student
  - Mike Woody
  - Speakers for Seminar, 1977
  - VU Spring Seminar, 1979
  - Spring Guest Lectures 1978- VU- GSM
  - Fiscal and Monetary Policy (Winter 1977) VU
  - Monetary Problems and Policies (Feb- Apr Spring 1976) VU Money and Banking Class 4/75, VU
  - International Finance Class (Fall 1975) VU
  - VU- GSM Associate, 1978
  - VU- EMBA Program
  - IPC- General File and Information
  - IPC- Scope and Function-, July 15, 1986 3-5
  - IPC- Meeting- Jan 25, 1988 3pm
  - IPC- Meeting-, Jul 20, 1987
  - IPC- Agenda Meeting- 8pm, Jan 6, 1988
  - IPC- Meeting, Jul 20, 1987
  - IPC- April 20, 1987 3pm Kings Room
  - IPC- Mar 12, 1987- Latin American Memo to Members
  - IPC-Jan 19, 1987 3pm
  - IPC- Oct 20, 1986 3pm
  - IPC-, Jul 14, 1986
  - IPC-, Apr 15, 1986
  - IPC-, Jan 21, 1986
  - IPC- Oct 15, 1985 7:30am
  - IPC- Jul 15, 1985 7:30-10:30am
  - IPC- 7/15/85 7:30 am
  - IPC-, 4/16/85
  - IPC-4/16/85 7:15 am
  - IPC- 10/16/84 7:15 am
  - IPC- 10/16/84 7:15 am
  - IPC-, 4/17/84
  - Commerce Union Bank- Daane, April 1984
  - IPC-, Oct 18, 1983
  - IPC-, April 19, 1983
  - IPC-, April 1983
  - IPC-, April 20, 1982
  - IPC- Material, April 20, 1982
  - IPC- Material, Oct 19, 1982
  - IPC- General Info – Old
  - IPC-, April 21, 1981
  - IPC-, Oct 20, 1981
  - Institute of International Finance
  - IPC-, Oct 21, 1980
  - IPC-, April 14, 1980
  - IPC-, Oct 15, 1979
  - IPC-, April 16, 1979
  - IPC- Oct 16, 1978 9am
  - IPC-, April 17, 1978
  - Bob Bennett- Econocast Services
  - Blackberry Farm
  - Misc. Blair School of Music Materials
  - Blair Patron Society- Development Materials
  - Blair Patron Society- Development Materials
  - Blair Patron Society- Development Materials
  - Blair Patron Society- Development Materials
  - Blair Patron Society- Development Materials
  - Luncheon- Governor Blanton, May 8, 1975
  - Meeting of Blair Key-Board- University Club Feb 13, 1986 Noon Erwin Blumenthal- Deutsche Bundesbank
  - Gregory E. Boscor
  - Long Bonds Meeting- Jan 10, 1978 10am- Currey’s Conference Room Booth Investments Forum (BII) 1984- Sep 8th – Vandy Plaza
  - Bob Booth Correspondence
  - J.C. Bradford and Co.
  - GN Brands Centrale Rabobank Correspondence
  - Armand Braun
  - Bretton Woods Committee- Correspondence
  - Bettie’s Work File- Bretton Woods Committee Annual Meeting Feb 16, 1988 Bretton Woods Committee Jun 24, 1986 Reception for Clausen and Conable Bretton Woods-, 1984
  - British Information Services
  - Brazil, 1985
  - Brookings Institute- Economic Choices-, 1986- May 28, 1986
  - Brookings Institute- Panel-, Sep 20, 1978
  - Brookings Institute- Program
  - Chairman Arthur F. Burns
  - Business International
  - Steve Buckles
  - Business Expo- Advisory Board 1/7/86 –Venture Tek 4:30
  - Business Expo- Advisory Board 1/28/86 4:30
  - Business Expo-Venture Tek Meeting- Info for Forum
  - Business Expo-1986 Jane Woodard President
  - Whittaker Board of Directors Meeting, 2/26/88
  - NFA- Director’s Meeting, May 19, 1988
  - NFA- Director’s Meeting, Nov 19, 1987
  - NFA- Director’s Meeting, May 21, 1987
  - NFA- Treasurer’s Report- Month of April 1987 and 10 months ended April 30, 1987 NFA- Budget Fiscal Year, 1988
  - NFA- Misc. Business Papers, 1987
  - NFA- Budget for Fiscal Year, 1988
  - NFA- Misc. Business Papers, 1987
- Lateral File #1 Drawer #5
  - NFA- Director’s Meeting, May 21, 1987
  - NFA- Treasurer’s Report for Month of April 1987 and 10 months ending, April 30, 1987
  - NFA- Budget for Fiscal 1988- Charts
  - NFA- Budget for Fiscal Year, 1988
  - NFA- Board of Directors Information 1987- Spring
  - NFA- Budget for Fiscal Year, 1988
  - NFA- Board of Directors Information 1987- Fall
  - NFA- Arbitrator’s Manual
  - NFA- Three Year Report-, Feb 1986
  - NFA- Board- Chicago May 19, 1988/ Whittaker Corp- LA, May 20, 1988
  - NFA- Board-Chicago Aug 25, 1988 2pm
  - NFA- 1988 Directors List
  - NFA- Treasurer’s Report, Jun 17, 1987
  - NFA- 1984-1985 Misc.
  - NFA- Finance Committee- Chicago Jan 12, 1988 3pm
  - NFA- Annual Meeting- NY, 2/25/88
  - NFA- Board Meeting- Chicago, May 21, 1987
  - NFA- Finance Committee- Chicago Oct 7, 1987 3:30pm
  - NFA- Board of Directors – NY, Aug 20, 1987
  - NFA- Finance Committee- Chicago, 4/2/87
  - NFA- Finance Committee- Mar 5, 1986- Boca Raton FL
  - NFA- Board of Directors- Chicago, Aug 21, 1986
  - NFA- Annual and Board- Washing to n, DC 2/27/86
  - NFA- Directors Meeting, 5/15/86
  - NFA- Chicago, May 23, 1985
  - NFA- Finance Committee- Chicago, April 24, 1985
  - NFA- Finance Committee- Chicago, Jan 17, 1985
  - NFA- Board of Directors- Chicago- Nov 17, 1988 3pm
  - Misc. Information
    - Alco Meetings- Loose Sovran Bank Info
    - Alco- Board Room 7:30-8:30 am
    - Alco Meeting- June 22, 1989 Board Room 7:30-8:30 Loose Sovran Bank Info
    - Alco Meeting 4/20/89 7:30 am Board Room
    - Alco Meeting 2/24/89 8:30-9:30 Board Room
    - Loose Sovran Bank Info
    - Alco- General Memos
    - Alco (Asset/Liability Management Committee) General File Alco Meetings (Asset/Liability Management Committee)
    - Alco Meeting- 9/22/88 Board Room 7:30 – 8:30 am Alco- 7/20/88 Board Room 7:30 am
    - Alco Meeting- 1/20/89 Board Room 7:30 am
  - Alco Meeting- 11/17/88 Board Room 7:30 am
  - Alco Meeting- 6/23/88 Board Room 7:30 am
  - Alco Meeting-, 5/19/99
  - Sovran Bank- Loose Materials
  - Alco- 3/17/88 Board Room 7:30- 8:30 am
  - Alco-, 2/18/88
  - Alco Meeting- 1/21/88 Board Room 7:30
  - Money Market- 1989 Money Market
    - Money Market Forecast, 1989
    - Money Market Forecasts, 1988
    - Money Market Forecast, 1987
    - Money Market Forecast Committee Meetings 4/14/86 Money Market Committee, 1986
    - Money Market Committee and Subgroup Info
    - Money Market, 1984-1985
  - Money Market Subgroup Forecasts, 1982-1983
  - Money Market Committee Meeting 5/10/76 Cancelled
  - Meeting with Bill Simms and Danny Bates re. Money Market, 7/12/76
  - Money Market Committee Meeting-, 4/12/76
  - Money Market Committee Meeting-, 2/25/76
  - Money Market Committee Meeting-, 12/3/75
  - Money Market Committee Meeting-, 10/23/75
  - Money Market Committee Meeting-, 9/23/75
  - Money Market Committee Meeting-, 9/8/75
  - Money Market Committee Meeting-, 8/27/75
  - Money Market Committee Meeting-, 8/20/75
  - NFA- Finance Committee, 4/14/88
  - NFA- Proposed Budget for Fiscal Year, 1989 (April 21, 1988)
  - NFA- Proposed Budget for Fiscal Year, 1989 (May 19, 1988)
  - NFA- 1988- Memo to Executive Committee re: Assessment Fees and Bylaws ABA- American Bankers Association- San Francisco, 10/25/86
    - Cocktail Reception Info
    - ABA Convention 10/17-21/87 Dallas (Did not attend)
    - ABA- San Francisco, 10/24-28/86
  - ABA-10/24-29/86- Envelope
  - ABA convention- Hawaii, 10/8-12/83
  - ABA Convention- Atlanta, 10/16-20/82
  - ABA Annual Convention- San Francisco, 10/3-7/81
  - Advantage Companies
  - Advantage- Editorial Advisory Board- Feb 6 12:00 Directors Correspondence Advantage- Nashville’s Business Monthly- Board Meeting, 1985
  - Advantage Magazine Editorial Advisory Board Meetings
  - Addresses- Daane Reception- NY
  - Advantage Magazine Advisory Committee Meeting 2/4/82 Advantage Magazine’s Editorial Advisory Board
  - Alfalfa Club Dinner- DC, 1/30/88
  - 74th Annual Alfalfa Club Dinner- DC, 1/31/87
  - 73rd Annual Alfalfa Club Dinner- DC, 1/25/86
  - 72nd Annual Alfalfa Club Dinner- DC, 1/26/85
  - 71st Annual Alfalfa Club Dinner- DC, 1/28/84
  - 69th Annual Alfalfa Club Dinner- DC, 1/23/82
  - 68th Annual Alfalfa Club Dinner-, DC 1/24/81
  - Alfalfa Club Dinner-, 1/26/80
  - Alfalfa Club Dinner Meeting – DC 1/21/78-Statler Hilton 7:15 pm